http://www.collegebound.net/privacy/

Privacy Policy
The CollegeBound Network Privacy Policy
Print this document | Close this window
Last Updated: 10/17/2017
This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from and about you when you visit our website collegebound.net or any other website or online service owned or operated by collegebound.net that links to this Privacy Policy (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy also explains how collegebound.net may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.
If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please first contact collegebound.net, Compliance Department,
2 Teleport Dr., Suite 201, Staten Island, NY 10314, (718) 761-4800, privacy@keys2winning.com.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Personal Information
The CollegeBound Network, or a third party service provider acting on our behalf ("Service Provider"), collects personal information from you when you choose to share it with us to use our matching services, create an online account with us, order products or services from us, request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email list, participate in a survey, or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, education level and year of graduation, information you include on your resume, and, credit card information such as credit card number and security number if you are a collegebound.net customer. We may combine your personal information with additional personal information and non-personal information we collect or receive about you from other online and offline sources.
Information Automatically Collected
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.
This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.
We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.
Information Collected From Other Sources
We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, updated contact information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity. We may combine this information with the information we collect from and about you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.
We may collect your location based information for the purpose of providing location-based products and services on JobHub. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you the service. If you no longer wish to allow us to track your geo-location information in the Mobile App you may turn this off at the device level.
INFORMATION USE
The CollegeBound Network or its Service Providers may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:
To fulfill orders, provide service and communicate with customers;
To develop new products or services;
To respond to your inquiries;
To provide you with customized Site content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Site or on other sites;
To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from our company or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
To contact you when necessary;
To obtain feedback on the quality of the communication you received from employment or educational organizations from whom you have requested information or we have matched based on your interests;
To review the usage and operations of our Site and services and improve our Site content, products and services;
To address problems with the Site, our business or our products and services;
To manage our telecommunications networks;
To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business;
As described to you at the point of data collection; and
To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud.
These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
We may contact you via email, telephone, text message, postal mail, or any other means of communication that you provide to us as a means of contacting you.
By creating an Account via membership to collegebound.net, you agree that collegebound.net may send you informational/marketing text (SMS) messages via an automatic telephone dialing system as part of the normal business operation of your use of the Services. You may opt-out of receiving text (SMS) messages From collegebound.net at any time by texting the word STOP to XXXX from the mobile device receiving the messages. You acknowledge that opting out of text (SMS) messages may impact your use of the Services. Please text the word HELP to XXXX, call (888)660.9060, or email privacy to receive more information. Members can expect an average of 6-8 text (SMS) message per month; standard Message & Data rate may apply. Consenting to the above terms is not an indication of purchase on the part of the user.
Our supporting carries include U.S. Cellular, T-Mobile, C Spire, Cincinnati Bell, Cricket, Carrie, AT&T, Carolina West, Cellcom, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Nextel, Sprint, and nTelos. Verizon, T-Mobile or Wireless carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by visiting our opt-out page.
INFORMATION DISCLOSURE
The CollegeBound Network may disclose the information we collect from and about you as only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy: (1) to the employment or educational organizations from whom you have requested information or the employment or educational organization we have matched based on your interests; (2) to our email, data hosting, and Short Message Service (SMS)/text messaging service providers, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the The CollegeBound Network
Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) in certain situations, collegebound.net may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements (5) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (6) to our selected partners and affiliates that we believe may have offers of interest to you; (7) as described to you at the point of collection and (8) to any other Third party with your prior consent to do so.
We do not sell your personal information to third parties. These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
The CollegeBound Network may share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties.
Also, The CollegeBound Network may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through this Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS: MARKETING AND "DO NOT TRACK"
If you are a California resident, you may opt-out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To opt out, please contact us at CAprivacy@keys2winning.com.
California residents may choose to opt-out of the sharing of their personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes at any time by submitting a request in writing to collegebound.net, Compliance Department, 1200 South Ave., Staten Island, NY 10314 or by e-mailing us the request at: CAprivacy@keys2winning.com. We honor all such opt-out requests and it is our policy not to share personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes where you have submitted such a request. It is important to note that this opt-out does not prohibit disclosures made for non-marketing purposes.
California law requires that we disclose how our site responds to "Do Not Track" (DNT) signals from browsers and other mechanism that express the user's preference not to be tracked. Currently, there is not an industry-wide accepted definition of what is a DNT signal. For this reason, we currently do not respond to such signals.
COOKIES AND DATA COLLECTION TECHNOLOGIES
Technologies such as: cookies or similar technologies are used by collegebound.net and our
affiliate partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
We use cookies to remember users' search criteria (e.g. zip code). Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
OPTING OUT OF INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISEMENTS
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.
If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
PUBLIC FORUMS
Any information you may disclose in our blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms when providing testimonials or product reviews, or on other public areas of the Site, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. To request removal of your personal information from our public areas of our Site, contact us at blogcomments@keys2winning.com.
In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Alternatively, if you used a third party application to post such information, you can remove it, by either logging into the said application and removing the information or by contacting the appropriate third party application.
Social Media (Features) and Widgets:
Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the Privacy Policy of the company providing it.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
The Site may have links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.
TESTIMONIALS
We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at privacy@keys2winning.com
OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
Protecting children's privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen.
OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY
We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.
No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.
Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at privacy@keys2winning.com
When you enter sensitive information our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Upon request collegebound.net will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information, please resubmit your new contact information along with your interests in certain employment or educational opportunities. If the Site uses an online account, you may sign in to your account and update your personal information. If you prefer that we no longer use your information to provide you with services, please visit our opt-out page. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at privacy@keys2winning.com.
collegebound.net
2 Teleport Drive, Suite 201
Staten Island, NY 10314
718-761-4800
REVISIONS TO THIS POLICY
The CollegeBound Network reserves the right to revise this policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you posted here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective.
